Morrow Family papers, 1839-1966
Sophia Smith Collection
- Lindbergh, Anne (Morrow)
  - Morrow, Elizabeth (Cutter)
    - Organizations and activities (Box 50)
      - Smith College
        - Alumnae House Fund
          - Building Committee
            - Correspondence and minutes, 1930-39, undated (Box 66, Folder 16-23)
            - Specifications (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
        - Sophia Smith homestead, 1931-38 (Box 67, Folder 3-4)
        - Correspondence
          - General
            - 1920-39 (Box 67, Folder 5-16)
            - 1940-1945-46 (A-J) (Box 68, Folder 1-13)
            - 1945-46 (K-Z)-48 (Box 69, Folder 1-18)
            - 1949-54, undated (Box 70, Folder 1-23)
          - Admission of Jewish students, 1947-48 (Box 70, Folder 24)
          - Alumnae College: The Americas, 1941 (Box 70, Folder 25)
          - Alumnae Council, Class of 1896, 1944-54 (Box 70, Folder 26)
          - Alumnae Fund, 1928-41 (Box 70, Folder 27)
          - Applications, 1937-41 (Box 71, Folder 1)
          - Capital Gifts, 1946-53 (Box 71, Folder 2)
          - Committee for Discrimination in Giving (anti-Communist letters), 1954 (Box 71, Folder 3)
          - Fact Sheet on College Scholarships, 1948 (Box 71, Folder 4)
          - Furnishings of President's house, 1939 (Box 71, Folder 5)
          - Grierson, Margaret, 1940-53 (Box 71, Folder 6-7)
          - Hankins, Frank: sex questionnaire controversy, 1926 (Box 71, Folder 8)
          - Neilson, William and Elisabeth (Muser) "Li"
            - General, 1918-43 (Box 71, Folder 9-10)
            - Portrait, 1939 (Box 71, Folder 11)
            - Successor, 1939 (Box 71, Folder 12)
          - Seelye, Laurenus Clark: telegram, 1908 (Box 71, Folder 13)
          - Women's Clubs, 1927-40 (Box 71, Folder 14)
        - Commencements and Reunions
          - 1897-1940 (Box 71, Folder 15-33)
          - 1941-52 (Box 72, Folder 1-14)
          - Songs, circa 1949, undated (Box 72, Folder 15)
        - Board of Trustees: RESTRICTED (Box 73-76)
      - Union Theological Seminary: Henry Sloan Coffin Fund (Box 77)
        - Fundraising materials and agendas, 1944-45 (Box 77, Folder 1)
        - Budget, 1945 (Box 77, Folder 2)
        - Correspondence, 1936-45, undated (Box 77, Folder 3-4)
        - Events, 1945 (Box 77, Folder 5)
        - Women's Committee
          - Lecture transcripts, 1951-52 (Box 77, Folder 6)
          - Prospect lists, 1945 (Box 77, Folder 7-8)
        - Printed material and news clippings, 1945-46 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - United Service Organizations (USO)
        - Calendar and pledge book, May-Jul 1942 (Box 77, Folder 10)
        - Administrative
          - Reports, 1941-44 (Box 77, Folder 11-13)
          - Committee on Review: report, draft, 1944 (Box 77, Folder 14)
          - Committee on Volunteer Service: agenda, 1945 (Box 77, Folder 15)
        - Fundraising campaign
          - Women's Division, 1942 (Box 77, Folder 16)
          - Joint War Appeal: greater New York, 1942 (Box 77, Folder 17)
          - Printed material, 1942 (Box 77, Folder 18)
          - Correspondence
            - A-Z, 1942 (Box 77, Folder 19-23)
            - Letters of thanks to ECM, 1942 (Box 77, Folder 24)
          - Sample appeal letters, 1942 (Box 77, Folder 25)
          - Events: campaign opening dinner, May 1942 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
          - News clippings, 1942 (Box 78, Folder 3-4)
        - Correspondence
          - 1943, 1945, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 5-12)
          - Sullivan, Dorothy: training course material, 1943 (Box 78, Folder 13)
          - Minneapolis USO, 1943 (Box 78, Folder 14)
          - Citizens' Committee of the USO, 1942 (Box 78, Folder 15)
          - Re: Negro experience in the USO, 1942 (Box 78, Folder 16)
        - Travel
          - Midwest, 7-22 Nov, 1943 (Box 78, Folder 17)
          - Tennessee and Mississippi, 13-20 Jan, 1945 (Box 78, Folder 18)
          - Texas, 1944 (Box 78, Folder 19)
          - Western, 21 Sep-17 Oct, 1944 (Box 78, Folder 20)
          - Portland, OR, 1944 (Box 78, Folder 21)
          - News clippings, 1943-45 (Box 78, Folder 22)
        - Printed material (Box 79)
          - "Social Mixers," circa 1941-44 (Box 79, Folder 1)
          - Brochures and programs, 1942-44 (Box 79, Folder 2)
          - "Sing-a-Song," and "Speakers' Handbook," circa 1941-44 (Box 79, Folder 3)
          - Play, "I Didn't Know" and other printed material, 1943 (Box 79, Folder 4)
          - Returning and wounded soldiers
            - Reports, 1944 (Box 79, Folder 5)
            - Volunteer training booklets, 1944, undated (Box 79, Folder 6-7)
            - "Understanding People in Wartime," "Community Service for Veterans," 1943-44 (Box 79, Folder 8)
            - "Are You Ready for His Return?" "After the War?," 1943-45 (Box 79, Folder 9)
            - Other printed material on return of soldiers, 1943 (Box 79, Folder 10)
          - Booklets on women, circa 1941-45 (Box 79, Folder 11)
          - Miscellaneous, 1941-46 (Box 79, Folder 12-14)
        - Speeches
          - Notes and typescripts for speeches by ECM, 1941-45 (Box 79, Folder 15-17)
          - Typescripts of remarks by Prescott Bush and Rockefeller, John D., Jr., 1942 (Box 79, Folder 18)
        - Notebook, 1943 (Box 79, Folder 19-23)
        - Volunteer training manual and correspondence, 1944 (Box 80, Folder 1)
        - State conferences of volunteers
          - Sample outline, 1944-45 (Box 80, Folder 2)
          - Summary of proceedings, Colorado Springs, Sep-Oct 1944 (Box 80, Folder 3)
          - New Jersey and Idaho state conferences, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 4)
          - "Planning Volunteer Conferences," 1945 (Box 80, Folder 5)
        - Photographs, 1943, undated (Box 80, Folder 6)
        - Victory Book Drive, Feb 1942 (Box 80, Folder 7)
        - Captain Colin Kelly portrait unveiling, 1942 (Box 80, Folder 8)
        - Smith College Student Committee for Defense and Reconstruction, 1942-43 (Box 80, Folder 9)
        - Englewood Committee of the USO, 1942 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - Other World War II-related organizations and activities
        - Aid to Britain
          - Printed material, 1940-41 (Box 80, Folder 11-18)
          - Correspondence and minutes, 1940-41 (Box 80, Folder 19)
          - Endorsement, 1940-41 (Box 80, Folder 20)
          - News clippings, 1933-1941 (Box 80, Folder 21-22)
        - America First Committee, 1940 (Box 80, Folder 23)
        - America's Fund for British Air Forces, 1940 (Box 80, Folder 24)
        - American Red Cross, 1941-42 (Box 80, Folder 25)
        - American Women's Volunteer Services, 1941-42 (Box 80, Folder 26)
        - Committee to Defend America, 1943 (Box 80, Folder 27)
        - East and West Association, 1942 (Box 80, Folder 28)
        - Federal Union, 1940-42 (Box 80, Folder 29-30)
        - Freedom House, 1943 (Box 81, Folder 1)
        - General
          - Correspondence
            - 1939-44 (Box 81, Folder 2)
            - Fortune magazine, 1934-40 (Box 81, Folder 3)
          - Articles and speeches, 1939-42 (Box 81, Folder 4)
        - International Student Service, 1940-42 (Box 81, Folder 5)
        - National Committee on the Cause and Cure of War, 1938-40 (Box 81, Folder 6)
        - National Emergency Committee, 1940 (Box 81, Folder 7)
        - National War Fund, Inc., 1943 (Box 81, Folder 8-9)
        - Non-Partisan Central Committee to Win the Peace, 1943 (Box 81, Folder 10)
        - Women's Action Committee, 1943 (Box 81, Folder 11)
        - Evacuation of English children, 1940 (Box 81, Folder 12)
        - Wartime appeal letters, 1940-43 (Box 81, Folder 13)
        - Unidentified memo on Russia-related tactics, undated (Box 81, Folder 14)
        - Gaspard Weiss
          - ECM's financial assistance to Weiss and Meyhoffer families, 1941-46 (Box 81, Folder 15)
          - Correspondence
            - From Mrs. Thomas I. Bennett, 1948 (Box 81, Folder 16)
            - ECM to GW, 1949-53 (Box 81, Folder 17)
            - Re Weiss arrival in America, 1947 (Box 81, Folder 18)
            - Weiss family to ECM, 1948-54 (Box 81, Folder 19-21)
            - To ECM about GW, 1947-50 (Box 81, Folder 22)
            - Letters of application, 1948 (Box 81, Folder 23)
            - ECM affidavit to colleges about GW, 1948-52 (Box 81, Folder 24)
          - General, 1948-1953 (Box 81, Folder 25)
          - Lecture, "Gaspard Weiss," 1950 (Box 81, Folder 26)
        - Endorsement of Wendell Wilkie, 1940 (Box 81, Folder 27)
        - Women's Army Auxiliary Corps, 1942 (Box 81, Folder 28)
      - United States National Commission for UNESCO, 1951-52 (Box 81, Folder 29)
      - Welfare and Relief Mobilization, 1932 (Box 81, Folder 30)
      - Welsh Choir (Box 82)
        - Administrative, 1937 (Box 82, Folder 1)
        - List of potential contributors, circa 1936-37 (Box 82, Folder 2)
        - Seat list, ticket correspondence, 1937 (Box 82, Folder 3-5)
        - Correspondence, A-Z, 1937 (Box 82, Folder 6-15)
        - Publicity, 1937 (Box 82, Folder 16-17)
        - Sample programs, 1937 (Box 82, Folder 18)
        - National Museum of Wales
          - Annual report, 1935-36 (Box 82, Folder 19)
          - Benefit, 1939 (Box 82, Folder 20)
        - Notes, 1937 (Box 82, Folder 21)
      - Young Women's Christian Association of the City of New York (YWCA)
        - Administrative
          - Constitution and bylaws, meeting minutes, 1922 (Box 82, Folder 22)
          - Statement of Work, 1920 (Box 82, Folder 23)
          - Convention reports, 1922 (Box 83, Folder 1)
          - Report by divisions of New York City campaign, Mar 1920 (Box 83, Folder 2)
          - National finance commission, 1920-22 (Box 83, Folder 3)
        - Correspondence
          - Outgoing, 1922-38 (Box 83, Folder 4)
          - Incoming, 1921-38 (Box 83, Folder 5)
          - General, 1920-66 (Box 83, Folder 6)
        - News clippings, 1922 (Box 83, Folder 7)
        - Printed material
          - 1920-22 (Box 83, Folder 8)
          - 1929-44 (Box 83, Folder 9)
        - Material for budget campaign, 1921-22 (Box 83, Folder 10)
        - New York City campaign, Dec 1921 (Box 83, Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous, 1921, undated (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - Other organizations
        - A-E, 1929-39 (Box 83, Folder 13)
        - F-M, 1930-54 (Box 83, Folder 14)
        - N, 1932-40 (Box 83, Folder 15)
        - O-Z, 1930-41 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Speeches and Writings
      - Unpublished writings
        - Diaries
          - 1883-99 (Box 83, Folder 17-19)
          - 1899-1915 (Box 84, Folder 1-8)
          - 1916-26 (Box 85, Folder 1-5)
          - 1927-36 (Box 86, Folder 1-5)
          - 1937-46 (Box 87, Folder 1-6)
          - 1947-54 (Box 88, Folder 1-5)
        - Essays (Box 89)
          - "Spring Term," 1896 (Box 89, Folder 1)
          - "A Blackberry Experience," undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
          - "Let Who Will Be Clever," undated (Box 89, Folder 3)
          - "St. Lawrence: the Story of an Italian Cat," undated (Box 89, Folder 4)
          - "Shakespeare's Treatment of the Supernatural Agents in Midsummer Night's Dream, Macbeth, and The Tempest and their relation to human beings," undated (Box 89, Folder 5)
          - "The Last Chronicle of Barset," probably for the Novel Club, Cleveland, 1899 (Box 89, Folder 6)
        - "Smith College Relief Unit," for the Red Cross: drafts and correspondence, undated (Box 89, Folder 7)
          - Little Brown House: memoir, undated (Box 89, Folder 8)
          - Untitled autobiographical manuscript, undated (Box 89, Folder 9-10)
        - Plays
          - "Three Times - and Out": play, undated (Box 89, Folder 11)
          - "A Puritan Family Dinner," 1920 (Box 89, Folder 12)
          - "Sara Speaks Out" for Missionary Society, undated (Box 89, Folder 13)
          - Thanksgiving Play, 30 Nov 1933 (Box 89, Folder 14)
        - Prayers: from ECM's journal, 1946-47 (Box 89, Folder 15)
        - Poetry
          - Poetry notebooks, undated (Box 89, Folder 16-19)
          - Miscellaneous poems, 1882, undated (Box 89, Folder 20)
          - Translation "Night's table," undated (Box 89, Folder 21)
      - Published Writing
        - Bibliography of works, undated (Box 89, Folder 22)
        - Review in Poetry of ECM's work, Jan 1928 (Box 89, Folder 23)
        - Letters from publishers, 1896-97 (Box 89, Folder 24)
        - "An Impression of Plato's Dialogues," Smith College Monthly, 1896 (Box 89, Folder 25)
        - Poems published in Smith College Monthly, 1895-96 (Box 89, Folder 26)
        - "A Loaf of Bread," Godey's Magazine, Feb 1896 (Box 90, Folder 1)
        - "Ivy Song," Smith College Monthly, Oct 1896 (Box 90, Folder 2)
        - "Tete-a-Tete," The Interlude, Feb 1897 (Box 90, Folder 3)
        - "Is a Masterpiece of Style.. ." The Interlude, May 1897 (Box 90, Folder 4)
        - "Two Views," The Interlude, May 1898 (Box 90, Folder 5)
        - "Memory - A Poem," The Interlude, May 1899 (Box 90, Folder 6)
        - "If I Could Take Your Tears, Love," lyrics by ECM, music by Patty Stair, Six Songs, 1900 (Box 90, Folder 7)
        - "Impressions of the Sorbonne," The Interlude, May 1901 (Box 90, Folder 8)
        - "Three Outside Seats," McClures Magazine, 1901 (Box 90, Folder 9)
        - "The Smith College Relief Unit," The Wellesley Alumnae Quarterly, Jan 1918 (Box 90, Folder 10)
        - "Experiences of Other Leaders of College Campaigns," The Wellesley Alumnae Quarterly, Jan 1921 (Box 90, Folder 11)
        - "Highroad," Voices, Mar 1924 (Box 90, Folder 12)
        - "The Proudest Fruit," Scribner's, May 1925 (Box 90, Folder 13)
        - Eleven Poets, Vol. I, New York: Vinal, 1925 (Box 90, Folder 14)
        - "Lot's Wife," Harper's, Mar 1926 (Box 90, Folder 15)
        - "Wall," Harper's, May 1926 (Box 90, Folder 16)
        - "Kings' Color," Scribner's, Aug 1926 (Box 90, Folder 17)
        - "This Pine Tree," Scribner's, Dec 1926 (Box 90, Folder 18)
        - "Youth Passes," Contemporary Verse, Mar 1927 (Box 90, Folder 19)
        - "St. Francis of Assisi," Voices, May 1927 (Box 90, Folder 20)
        - "Atlas," Century, Aug 1927 (Box 90, Folder 21)
        - "The Singing Kettle" and four other poems, 1928 (Box 90, Folder 22)
        - "Seville in Summer," Saturday Review of Literature, 24 Aug 1929 (Box 90, Folder 23)
        - "The Maguey," Harper's, Nov 1930 (Box 90, Folder 24)
        - The Painted Pig 1930
          - Reprint, 1949 (Box 90, Folder 25)
          - Book with dedication to William Allan Neilson, 1930 (Box 90, Folder 26)
          - Marketing, 1930 (Box 90, Folder 27)
          - Typescript, 1930 (Box 90, Folder 28)
          - Newspaper clippings, 1930 (Box 90, Folder 29)
          - Correspondence
            - A-I, 1930-32 (Box 90, Folder 30)
            - J-Z, 1930-32 (Box 91, Folder 1)
            - From fans, 1930 (Box 91, Folder 2)
        - Review of Stuart Chase's Mexico, New York Herald Tribune, 9 Aug 1931 (Box 91, Folder 3)
        - "Our Street in Cuernavaca," American Mercury, Aug 1931 (Box 91, Folder 4)
        - Quatrains for My Daughter (Knopf) 1931 (Box 91)
          - Book, 1931 (Box 91, Folder 5)
          - Book with dedication to Annie Spencer Cutter, Sr., 1931 (Box 91, Folder 6)
          - Correspondence with publisher, 1931 (Box 91, Folder 7)
          - Typescripts
            - Poems, 1931 (Box 91, Folder 8)
            - With typewritten notes, 1931 (Box 91, Folder 9)
            - Copy for printer from notebook, 1931 (Box 91, Folder 10)
          - Reviews, 1931 (Box 91, Folder 11)
          - Correspondence, 1931-32 (Box 91, Folder 12)
        - Casa Mañana (1932)
          - Correspondence with publisher, 1932 (Box 91, Folder 13)
          - Book with dedication to Ada, Jan 1933 (Box 91, Folder 14)
        - "A Defense of College Women," New York Herald Tribune, 19 Nov 1933 (Box 91, Folder 15)
        - "Campaigning for Children," Child Welfare League Bulletin, Dec 1933 (Box 91, Folder 16)
        - Beast, Bird and Fish: An Animal Alphabet (1933)
          - Book, 1933 (Box 91, Folder 17)
          - Manuscript, 1933 (Box 92, Folder 1)
          - Illustrations and correspondence with Rene d'Harnoncourt, 1933 (Box 92, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 92, Folder 3)
          - Reviews, 1933 (Box 92, Folder 4)
        - "Three Poems," Atlantic Monthly, Apr 1934 (Box 92, Folder 5)
        - "Harried House," poem, The Forum and Century, and correspondence and draft of "In Taxco's Sun," Nov-Dec 1934 (Box 92, Folder 6)
        - "In Taxco's Sun," The Forum and Century, Dec 1934 (Box 92, Folder 7)
        - Obituary of Sara Dana Loomis, The Englewood Press, 5 Oct 1939 (Box 92, Folder 8)
        - A Pint of Judgment: a Christmas Story (Knopf) 1939
          - Book, 1939 (Box 92, Folder 9)
          - Proof, 1939 (Box 92, Folder 10)
        - The Rabbit's Nest, (Macmillan) 1940 (Box 92, Folder 11)
        - Correspondence related to publications, 1940-42 (Box 92, Folder 12)
        - Shannon (Macmillan) 1941
          - Manuscript and correspondence with publishers, 1941 (Box 92, Folder 13)
          - Correspondence from fans, 1941 (Box 92, Folder 14)
        - My Favorite Age (Macmillan) 1943
          - Book, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 15)
          - Correspondence with publisher, 1941-44 (Box 92, Folder 16)
          - Correspondence with fans, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 17)
          - Manuscript, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 18)
          - Drafts, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 19)
          - "Worst Girl in Town" (Box 92, Folder 20)
          - "Father Never Gets a Valentine" (Box 92, Folder 21)
          - "The General's Halo" (Box 92, Folder 22)
          - "Cooky Hill" (Box 93, Folder 1-2)
          - Illustrations (Box 93, Folder 3)
        - Tribute to Emily Brinckerhoff Duncan, 6 Oct 1945 (Box 93, Folder 4)
        - Youth Replies, I Can: Stories of Resistance, by May Lamberton Becker with foreword by ECM, 1945 (Box 93, Folder 5)
        - "Freedom without Food?" The Woman's Press, Jul-Aug 1945 (Box 93, Folder 6)
        - "President Neilson of Smith," Atlantic Monthly, Nov. 1946
          - Magazine, Nov 1946 (Box 93, Folder 7)
          - Notebook (Box 93, Folder 8)
          - Outline and scraps, 1st version (Box 93, Folder 9)
          - Drafts (Box 93, Folder 10-13)
          - Correspondence/source material, 1946 (Box 93, Folder 14)
          - General correspondence, 1946-47 (Box 93, Folder 15)
          - Correspondence A-Z, 1946-47 (Box 93, Folder 16)
          - Draft of Smith College Board of Trustees' record on Neilson's death, 1946 (Box 93, Folder 17)
          - Related articles (Box 93, Folder 18)
          - Speech by Neilson, circa 1930-31 (Box 93, Folder 19)
        - Copyrights, 1951-53 (Box 93, Folder 20)
        - "Party at the Palace," Smith College Alumnae Quarterly, Nov 1953 (Box 93, Folder 21)
        - The Mexican Years: Leaves from the Diary of Elizabeth Cutter Morrow, signed for Charles from Grandma Bee, 1953 (Box 94, Folder 1)
        - "A Cruise on the Mouette" by grandchildren, undated (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Speeches
        - Opening of new buildings at Englewood Hospital, 6 Jun 1915 (Box 94, Folder 3)
        - Red Cross Campaign, Englewood, 1918 (Box 94, Folder 4)
        - Grads' Day at Milton School, 12 Jun 1919 (Box 94, Folder 5)
        - "How Women Must Succeed" at League of Women Voters, 9 Feb 1922 (Box 94, Folder 6)
        - "What Are They Thinking About?" on travels to England, France, and Scotland, 1922 (Box 94, Folder 7)
        - "Theory of Poetry," Poetry Society, 1923 (Box 94, Folder 8)
        - Speech for Coolidge, 26 Feb and 28 Apr 1924 (Box 94, Folder 9)
        - Speech for Coolidge, Colony Club, 14 Oct 1924 (Box 94, Folder 10)
        - Debate: Colony Club versus Junior League, 19 Jan 1925 (Box 94, Folder 11)
        - "The Importunate Widow," St. John the Baptist School, 18 Mar 1926 (Box 94, Folder 12)
        - 30th Anniversary of Cleveland Novel Club, Dec 1926 (Box 94, Folder 13)
        - Girl Scouts Convention in New York, 29 Sep 1927 (Box 94, Folder 14)
        - Mary Moore's dinner for ECM on leaving for Mexico, 1 Oct 1927 (Box 94, Folder 15)
        - "On Mexico" for Poetry Society, circa 1928 (Box 94, Folder 16)
        - On Naval Conference, 11 Apr 1930 (Box 94, Folder 17)
        - Essex County Women's Republican Club (Radio), 3 Nov 1930 (Box 94, Folder 18)
        - Little School Parents, 11 Jan 1932, repeated 15 Apr 1937 (Box 94, Folder 19)
        - Englewood Community Chest, 9 Nov 1933 (Box 94, Folder 20)
        - "Preparation, Belief, and Faith as Essentials in Solicitation," 16 Nov 1933 (Box 94, Folder 21)
        - On Naval Conference, Council of Churches, 2 May 1934 (Box 94, Folder 22-23)
        - Dinner in honor of Douglas G. Thomson, 3 May 1934 (Box 94, Folder 24)
        - Flora Stone Mather Commencement, 13 Jun 1934 (Box 94, Folder 25)
        - "College graduate and the new leisure," Seven Women's Colleges radio broadcast, 22 Oct 1934. Reprinted in Smith College Alumnae Quarterly. (Box 94, Folder 26)
        - Community Chest, Orange, New Jersey, 1 Nov 1934 (Box 94, Folder 27)
        - Community Chest, Englewood, 15 Nov 1934 (Box 94, Folder 28)
        - Caroline Bacon Room at New School, 6 Nov 1935 (Box 94, Folder 29)
        - Englewood Community Chest, 12 Nov 1936 (Box 94, Folder 30)
        - Englewood Community Chest, 4 Nov 1937 (Box 94, Folder 31)
        - United Hospital Workers, Biltmore Hotel, New York City, 23 Nov 1937 (Box 94, Folder 32)
        - "The Lengthening Shadow," Women's Society, Englewood Chapter, 26 Oct 1938 (Box 94, Folder 33)
        - "The Amateur Poet," Cosmopolitan Club luncheon, 7 Feb 1939 (Box 94, Folder 34)
        - "Does America Deserve a Miracle?" radio speech 4 Jun 1940; distributed by Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies
          - Text (Box 94, Folder 35)
          - Correspondence re speech
            - Against speech, Jun 1940 (Box 94, Folder 36)
              [1 folder]
            - In favor, 1940 (Box 94, Folder 37-38)
            - In favor (cont'd), 1940 (Box 95, Folder 1)
            - Regarding Charles Lindbergh, 1940 (Box 95, Folder 2)
            - Received at Smith College, Jun-Jul 1940 (Box 95, Folder 3)
            - Received at Englewood or North Haven, 1940 (Box 95, Folder 4)
          - Newspaper clippings and song, 1940 (Box 95, Folder 5)
        - Englewood Community Chest, 15 Oct 1940 (Box 95, Folder 6)
        - Wilkie meeting, Englewood, 24 Oct 1940 (Box 95, Folder 7)
        - Cleveland Community Fund, 7 Nov 1940 (Box 95, Folder 8)
        - 50th Anniversary of Boston College Club, 18 Nov 1940 (Box 95, Folder 9)
        - Phi Beta Kappa dinner at Radcliffe, 13 Dec 1940. Repeated at Citizens' Dinner Committee for Four City Colleges, 26 Jan 1942 (Box 95, Folder 10)
        - Lend-Lease Bill, 8 Mar 1941 (Box 95, Folder 11)
        - "Politeness of the Mind, or, Intellectual Good Manners," Dwight School Commencement, 4 Jun 1941 (Box 95, Folder 12)
        - "The Defenseless Graduate," Dwight Morrow High School Commencement, 24 Jun 1941 (Box 95, Folder 13)
        - "Brave Women and Fair Men," NBC radio speech, printed in leaflet, 21 Nov 1941 (Box 95, Folder 14)
        - Citizens' Dinner Committee, Board of Higher Education, NY, 26 Jan 1942 (Box 95, Folder 15)
        - Calvary Church, Cleveland, 22 May 1942 (Box 95, Folder 16)
        - First WAACS reception, New York Herald Tribune party, 9 Jul 1942 (Box 95, Folder 17)
        - "Lasting Effects of Women's War Activities," New York Herald Tribune Forum on Current Problems, 17 Nov 1942 (Box 95, Folder 18)
        - Englewood Community Chest, Nov 1942 (Box 95, Folder 19)
        - Red Cross Special Gifts Committee, 3 Mar 1943 (Box 95, Folder 20)
        - National War Fund, Women's Division, opening campaign, 18 Oct 1943 (Box 95, Folder 21)